

Macsym

Krivyi

Contact

Address:

Kievska, Ternopil, Ukraine

Email:

champion5star247963@gmail.com

Skype:

live:.cid.8ad0146f263d770c

Skills

- React JS
- React Native
- Vue.js
- Express.js
- Laravel
- Node.js
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Python
- PHP
- MongoDB

Language

- English C1
- Russian A

Summary

Senior Front-end developer with over 6 years of experience in software development across various industries, with the 5 most recent years focused on React and React Native. I am well-respected amongst industry-leading companies as a skilled developer who truly understands the client infrastructure and pain points. I also have the hands-on, technical aptitude needed to design and build out solutions.

Skill Highlights

- User friendly UX/UI
- API building and Integration
- Soket IO
- Database design

Experience

Front-end Developer (UX and UI) - 07/2018 to 03/2021 ITM HOUSE, Toronto, Canada

- Developed an iOS and Android app to allow students in Belgium to apply for work.
- Developed a PWA for recruiters to match with students.
- Built a continuous integration workflow to test and deploy the apps.

Senior React Developer - 07/2015 to 10/2017

NOVISMART TECH., Wien, Austria

- Worked on large-scale React apps.
- Maintained large-scale JavaScript apps.
- Created and deployed React Native apps.
- Worked closely with the product/design team.
- Reviewed and kept code quality high.

Education

Bachelor of Degree in ${\bf Computer\ Science}$ - 2013

Kyiv National University of Technologies and Design,

Kyiv, Ukraine

2008 - 2013

Certification

Certified Web and Mobile Application Developer

Provider: SMTP Issued: January 2020